drobo.com 2013-05-26

# Drobo Privacy Policy

This Drobo, Inc. Privacy Policy (the "Policy") is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our websites and domains, including www.drobo.com and any other sites on the World Wide Web owned or operated by Drobo, Inc. (collectively, the "Site"). This Policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and the needs of our customers and partners. If we make a change to this Policy, we will post the updated Policy here. 

By using the Site, you agree to the terms of use posted on the Site ("Terms of Use"). If you do not agree to the Terms of Use, please do not use the Site. 

If you have any questions, comments, or requests regarding privacy, please send us an email at [privacy@drobo.com](mailto:privacy@drobo.com)

### Collection of Information

When you visit our Site, we collect non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways, including tracking your activities through your IP address or most-recently-visited URL. 

We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily submit such information to us, such as by ordering online, filling out a form or survey, requesting information from us, subscribing to marketing or support materials, registering yourself or your Drobo, Inc. products, entering a contest or sweepstakes, applying for a job at Drobo, Inc., registering your email address with us or emailing us. We may also collect personal information from you at other points on our site that state that personal information is being collected.

If you use our "tell a friend" feature, we will ask you for your friend's email address, and automatically send your friend one email inviting your friend to visit our Site. 

### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly, nor do we wish to obtain personally identifiable information from children who are using our site unsupervised. Thus, we ask children to obtain the consent of their parent or guardian before providing us with any personally identifiable information.

### Disclosure of Information

Unless we tell you otherwise, we do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to any third parties. Drobo, Inc. does retain service providers and suppliers to deliver products, services and customer solutions and to assist us with marketing and communication initiatives, and we might share your personally identifiable information with these business partners. These business partners are required by contract to keep confidential the information received on behalf of Drobo, Inc. and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Drobo, Inc. We may sell and rent aggregated (non-personally identifiable) information about our users. 

Testimonials posted on our Site are only posted with the expressed permission of the individual or company who provided that testimonial.

### Use of Information

We use personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information for internal marketing purposes, for order fulfillment, registration and support, and for site administration. However, unless we tell you otherwise, we usually do not use personally identifiable information collected from the Web site to send unsolicited mailings to you. Of course, if applicable, we do use personally identifiable information to perform the services for which such data was collected (i.e., if you sign up for an email newsletter, we will send the email newsletter to the address you provide us).

### Third Party Sites

The Policy only addresses our activities from our Site. We are not responsible for the content or practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as points to information on topics that may be useful to the user of our Site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Site to another Web site, the Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites that have a link on our Site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

### Cookies and Other Tracking Methods

When you view our website or advertisements, we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site, to help you navigate a website as easily as possible. Cookies can help us provide information that is targeted to your interests and they allow us to better understand how users use our site, which in turn helps us focus our resources on features that are most popular with our users. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site, including that portion which is targeted for our Registered Customers, may not work properly in that case.

### Security

We use industry-standard methods to protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access. Among other techniques, we usually store such information on a computer behind our "firewall" in a secure location, and we often restrict the number of employees internally who can access such data. Of course, there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet

### International Users

By visiting our Site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, such data may be stored on servers located in the United States or in countries in which our business partners are situated. By providing us with your data, you consent to such transfer and storage of such data.

### Removal of Your Personally Identifiable Data

If you provide us with personally identifiable information to have us perform ongoing services to you, usually we will provide you with a way to remove such data. Unfortunately, to the extent that such information is also stored in other databases, we cannot always ensure that such corrections or deletions will reach the other databases. If you wish to have information that you provided to us online removed from our records, please send us an email at [privacy@drobo.com](mailto:%20privacy@drobo.com).

We will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that your information is removed from our online records.

However, in the event that you subsequently provide Drobo, Inc. with your personally identifiable information through our Site, trade shows, webcasts, and/or other Drobo, Inc. events, we will assume that you have opted back into receiving communication from Drobo, Inc. You may send another email to [privacy@drobo.com](mailto:privacy@drobo.com) to be removed from our records.
